[GIRL] Wow, it's dark in here.
- Now it's too bright.
- [MAN] File 82-7-0-2.
Agent Rick Dicker interrogating.
State your name.
Kari McKeen. It's like Carrie,
only with a K instead of a C,
and an "ah" instead of an "a",
only one R, and an I instead of an I-E.
Tell me about the incident.
Well, it started out like any
normal sitting gig, you know,
with the reassuring
of the parent and all.
Mrs Parr, I can handle anything
this baby can dish out.
Can't I, little boo boo?
- Who can handle it? Mrs Parr?
- [LINE GOES DEAD]
Well, she knows
you're in good hands.
Now, who's ready
for some neurological stimulation?
Huh?
[COOING] Mama mama mama.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
It's time for cognitive develop...
[DELIGHTED SCREAM]
Who's the goo-goo baby?
Where's the hiding... huh?
That was really weird.
Wait right here.
[RINGING, BEEP]
Hello, Mrs Parr, this is Kari.
I have a question about Jack-Jack.
Can you call me? Aah!
[BABBLING]
Jack-Jack. Baby? Where are you?
Where are... Aah!
Mrs Parr, it's me. Jack-Jack is fine,
but weird things are happening,
and you need to tell me what to do,
'cause I'm... [GASPS]
- [JACK-JACK GIGGLES]
- How'd you get...? [SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS, GASPS]
[PANTING]
[LAUGHING]
- [GASPS]
- [DELIGHTED SCREAM]
[COOING, LAUGHS]
We're gonna calm things down
a bit now,
and look at flash cards.
- Won't that be fun?
- [LAUGHS]
- Triangle.
- [BABBLES]
- Good. House.
Good. Campfire.
Ah...
- [SCREAMS]
- [LAUGHING]
Ah! Don't panic.
Baby on fire. Baby on fire.
[COOING, LAUGHING]
Good baby! Nice baby.
[BABBLING]
[LAUGHS]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
- Yes?
- Is this the Parr's residence?
[LAUGHS] Yes. I'm Kari, the babysitter.
Well, hello, Kari. I'm...
You're my replacement.
Thank heaven you've come!
What does "S" stand for?
For sitter. Yeah, sitter.
Originally, I was gonna have
initials for babysitter,
but I would have been going around
wearing a big "BS".
You understand why
I couldn't go with that.
- And you believed him?
- The baby was exploding!
You ever sit an exploding baby
before, Mr Dicker?
- What's that?
- Have you told anyone about this?
- Your parents?
- They thought I was being funny.
But you believe me,
don't you, Mr Dicker?
- Sure, kid.
- I wish I could forget the whole thing.
You will, kid.
You will.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MUSIC ENDS]
- [JACK-JACK] Ga ga!
[LAUGHS]